This is probably my favorite website
I've ever built with Claude. This is the
AI Automation Society site. What I think
is so cool about this one is look at the
layers as I start to scroll. We can see
the mountains in the background and this
like treeine and they are clearly
different layers and that adds a really
premium feel as well as this whole
laptop kind of being dynamic. Right now
we keep scrolling down and we see a
little bit about AI automation society.
We see the words come in. We see the
words come in down here and we can flip
between the classroom live calls events
and leaderboard. And as we keep
scrolling, more text keeps coming in
dynamically and these cards start to
stack on top of each other, which I
think just feels super super dynamic and
engaging. We can see the pricing section
here, free community plus community, as
well as our certification cohort. We see
some Q&A down here or FAQ, sorry. And
look at this animation where the text
sort of like locks as we switch between
these different things. I think that's
awesome. We see some YouTube videos and
then finally the call to action down
here with once again the layering comes
back in. And I just think that that is
so so cool. And I know you guys are
probably wondering on mobile. So here it
is right here. This is me on my phone.
We get the same dynamic laptop screen.
We get the same layered effect, which I
think is just beautiful. We can scroll
through this text. We see we get these
same animations, but we click through
these sections a little bit differently.
We continue to scroll down. All of this
stuff comes in. The cards don't stack
the same way it does on desktop, but I'm
sure we could engineer that if we wanted
to with just one prompt. We keep coming
through. The point I'm trying to make
here is Fable 5.1 is able to take care
of this on mobile as well and you get
the exact same premium feel. I think
that this website is beautiful. Let's
take a look at another example here.
This is my website. You can see we've
got the text. We've got the hero
section. Those numbers were sort of like
ticking up. I've got myself over here
and this is like a really neat
background that I think adds depth and
adds another layer, but it's not
distracting. These are all clickable
links. These numbers are ticking up and
we can still see consistency with the
background animation. We continue to go
through these things color up as I
highlight. We get into this interesting
like dynamic element. You can see when I
move my mouse, these move, but once
again, it's not too overwhelming or
distracting. I think it just feels very
premium and adds some nice depth here.
We have a little bit and background
information. And this links to the about
page, which is um just a little bit of a
bio. It's nothing too fancy at all. But
anyways, we keep coming down and we have
like a little bit of a photo montage.
These kind of come up as they go into
screen. And then we keep coming down.
see my book, Becoming AI Native. We have
new YouTube videos every week. And then
it pulls up um join AIS and a little
signature, which it just actually found
in my um pictures on my local desktop.
Now, what I also really like is that the
navbar stays with you all the way
through. And it also did that within the
AIS um site, which I really, really
like. I don't know why. It just feels a
bit more like having it locked there
just feels good. Now, let me show you
guys this next one, which is Glido. I
think this one is so cool because look
at this little dictation bar. There's so
many animations within this. You can see
that it's dictating words and putting
them into Slack. And this looks very
similar to the way that you can actually
see me talking into my mic right now.
And right here, you can see that I'm
dictating with Glyo. So, super super
cool. We can have the apps right here
that we already use and it pauses when
I'm on it. We get these animations
coming in with the holding down a key
saying it messy and then it gets
dictated and pasted over here. Much
cleaner. We can keep going down and
seeing that we have different apps like
we're seeing Glido putting this into
Slack. We're seeing Glido put this into
cursor. We're seeing it actually sort of
like have these animations where we can
see what it would look like to use GLO
in these different apps. Gmail and of
course cloud code in the terminal. We
have more stuff down here transcribing
over here or speaking over here as well
as just like typing the difference right
there. And now this is my favorite part.
As we go down, which is this animation,
we have the dictation and then we have
these two things that are going
different ways with all of these apps.
Some of these logos are obviously off,
but hey, for a oneshot prompt, this is
pretty solid. I like that animation,
too. And we have some stuff from us, the
founders down here. Anyways, the
pricing. Now, what I want to talk about
is how do you actually get Fable 5.1 to
do stuff like this without giving you AI
slop. Now, obviously, what I found is
having things like scroll animations and
having text feel more dynamic. And
specifically in this video, I really
found out about layering. That helps a
ton. But ultimately what I realized is
that you can't just say to Fable 5.1 or
any AI model, make this look
professional. Make this feel premium.
You really have to give it something to
work off of. So what we did in this
video is I got a lot of inspiration from
other websites. So for example, with
this website which I just absolutely
love, I found an example of a website
that I really loved and I took the
elements from it that I liked. So this
one is called Fora. You can see it's
very similar. You can see it has hero
text. It has the layers in the
background. Then when I started to
scroll, I was like, "Wow, I love the
layering here." So I told Fable 5.1 how
to figure out how we could make a hero
section that as I scroll down, there's
like four layers. There's a back
mountain, there's a middle mountain,
there's a laptop screen, and then
there's a front layer of trees. And I
basically just love that feel and I
wanted to replicate it. So I just had it
make all of these separate layers that
move when you scroll. Then we of course
have like this text thing. I really
liked how the cards here stacked. I
thought that that felt super premium.
So, I looked at this website for
inspiration and I told Fable 5.1 that I
wanted to have mine have the same feel
and I explained all the elements of this
and why I liked it and how I wanted it
to use that as inspiration. Now, for my
website here, there wasn't exactly a
website that I took inspiration from,
but instead what I did is I took
components that I really liked. So, I
went to um where is it? I went to
something called 21st.dev, which you
guys have probably heard of before
already if you've been watching me for a
while making sites. This site basically
has a bunch of components that you can
find and you can literally give your AI
agents the prompts for these animations.
So for example, this container scroll,
you can just copy prompt and then your
agent can basically copy that element.
So I was looking at backgrounds that I
really liked here. I was looking at
different gradients. I was looking at
different interactive elements and I
just decided that I liked one. I'm not
going to be able to find it right now,
but I really liked that one that you see
in the background here and I just took
it and then I started designing with it.
And then I just explained to Fable that
I wanted all of this text to sort of
appear as it enters the screen. And then
I said, "Hey, I want this to be 3D. I
want this to feel dynamic. I want, you
know, all this text to come in. I want
this to scroll sideways." And of course,
I used my scroll craft skill, which you
guys can access for completely free. It
is linked in my free school community,
which is in the description. This skill
has all of the design elements that you
need to understand for layering, for
scrolling, for, you know, text appearing
like this, for text appearing like this.
It has basically all these principles
inside of that skill. It's completely
free. And then for GLO, what I actually
did is we looked at a competitor site.
So we looked at Lemon, which is another
dictation app, and I loved how it had
these animations that almost give you
the feel as if you're already using the
product. So I basically just once again
came through here and said, "Hey,
actually, for this one, what I want you
to do is go to Glido. I want you to take
our brand guidelines and just insert it
onto a page like this." And you can see
this one was, you know, very directly
just like cloning it, I would say. But
that's what's so cool about Fable 5.1 is
it can inspect what's going on here and
it can generate you one that feels the
exact same. It even made the same sort
of like it almost feels like watercolor
painting in the background as you can
see, but it made the same vibe. And now
we just have Oh, sorry that was the
wrong app. And now we just have this
that we could go ahead and, you know,
push live if we wanted to. And then look
at what else I did. I was like, "Okay,
this is pretty cool." So I gave it an
example of a good site. And then I gave
it this goal, so one shot prompt. And
then I told it to build me two
distinctly different but most impressive
scrollcraft, which is my skill layered
sites that you could possibly build me
using our skills. I told it to look at
the AIS site cuz I really liked that
one. I told it to grab components from
21st.dev. I told it to go to
godly.websites. This is all about giving
your agent more specific prompts and
inspiration. If I go to actually godly
websites, you can see godly.design. We
can find trending sites. We can find um
logos. We can find hero sections. We can
give all of this kind of stuff to our AI
agents for inspiration of how we want
our site to look. CTAs, footers, OG
images. There's so much stuff in here.
There's also another site called awards
where you can literally look at websites
that are winning awards for design and
you can just understand what kind of
feel do you want. You know, there's
different categories in here um you know
technology, e-commerce, restaurant,
fashion because obviously your site
probably is going to convert better if
it feels like it's in your niche talking
to your avatar. So, this kind of stuff
helps you get inspiration much better.
There's literally another site called
Motion Sites that has like these
jaw-dropping animated backgrounds that
you can actually go ahead and grab and
just bring right into your websites. I
think the one that I actually used was
very similar to this one. If you, as you
can see, if I put this into a new page,
this one is just kind of like a really
nice animated background. It's obviously
not the same because ours is sort of
interactive, but this is also a really
cool feel to have in the background of
your hero section. Okay. Okay. So then
what I did is I gave it this /goal
prompt and I said, "Hey, I need you to
build me two distinctly different but
most impressive scrollcraft, which is my
skill type of sites that you could using
these skills, using layering, looking at
these components for inspiration, right?
Like godly websites, 21st.dev, looking
at all this type of stuff." I told her
it could generate the assets that it
needed. It could use key, it could use
Higsfield, it can use whatever it wants,
but I need it to be subtle but premium.
And I just said, "Go make me these
sites." So let's take a look at what it
actually built. So, this first one's
called Ferna, fresh herbs without the
window sill. You can already see right
away from the beginning, we have
layering. We can literally tell that
this plant PNG as well as I think even
this leaf in the background and these
leaves, they're all on different planes.
And the background image is on a
different layer as well. So, that gives
it a really nice immersive feel. We can
see the text comes through right here.
This text pops through. This text fades
in. These cards stack, which I think
looks amazing. We can see right here we
have a little scroll video now where
this literally grows over time and we
can go backwards. I like how this feels.
Once again, we get more layering. You
can see the plants in the background are
moving to the left as well, but not at
the same rate. And then finally, we end
off with this video where the light
basically turns on and that is the site.
That was a oneshot prompt with
Scrollcraft. Okay. And then the second
one it made, this one is called Lowkey.
It's a keyboard. Let me just refresh
this. So we see the text comes in like
that. We can see there's a little
animation here. It looks like there was
like some of the keys were being
pressed. If you watch right here, yep,
they look like they're being pressed. We
can keep scrolling and now we get more
elements of layering because the
background is moving as well as the
actual keyboard. Now, this is something
I don't like. You can see there's like a
hard cut right here. So, on more of a
verification loop and on more of like a
iteration, it would probably we'd be
able to fix that, but this was a oneshot
prompt. Anyways, text comes down here.
Text comes through here. I like how it
comes in like that. Same thing. Now,
open it. The keyboard keeps coming down.
And now the keyboard like comes out,
right? So it literally like takes it
apart itself and we can see inside of
it. And then we have different colors to
pick from. The desk is still scrolling
down this whole time. The keyboard comes
back and now we could also have our call
to action down here. So all things
considered, one shot prompts these two
sites. I think that it gives you a
really good base to work from. So after
showing you guys those examples and
talking about all that, here's what I
think is the most important that you
need to actually be doing when you're
building websites. And all of these
things that I'm going to talk about are
baked into my scroll craft skill, which
you can grab, like I said, in my free
school community. So, the first thing
that I think is really important is to
actually have some sort of brand
guidelines, right? You want this to feel
consistent as far as, you know, your
logo, your colors, things like that.
From there, I think that you need to
give it your three Ps, which is what I
call sort of like the AI monetization
readiness assessment. Meaning, does your
business have a pain that you're
solving? Do you have a person that
you're solving that pain for? And do you
have a promise of how your product or
service is solving that pain? Promising
how it solves that pain for that
specific person. Now, from there, what I
think you need is you need some sort of
scroll um lock. And maybe lock wasn't
the right word, but you need
responsiveness. You need the user to
feel that they're controlling the site
because as they scroll, they're getting
some sort of feedback. And it doesn't
have to be anything super super flashy.
But like even just having the text go
like this, even just having, you know,
words appear. And I have to refresh this
because they already did. Even having
the words appear like this, just
something that subtle, I think makes the
website feel so much more premium
because some feedback I got on my last
video was like, "Oh, I hate these 3D
world where I scroll and it makes me fly
through." And I get that. I get that. It
depends on the business. It depends on
the three Ps like I just said. But I do
think that having a scroll element in
something is just really, really
important. Anyways, from there, I think
that you need inspiration. I think it's
very hard to go into a website design
project and just tell it what you want
and expect that it's going to come back
and not feel like AI slot because unless
you're using some sort of skill or
unless you're building off of some sort
of template, it's probably going to feel
that way because AI is AI. So,
inspiration can come in the form of
looking at other websites and finding
out what you like about it, like the
layering. I think the layering is super
important like that. Maybe it's the way
that the pricing section feels. Maybe
it's the way that the background is like
interactive and responsive to the mouse.
Whatever it is, you need at least a
little bit of inspiration. And what's
cool about something like 21st.dev is
you can get inspiration on your borders.
You can get inspiration on your actual
buttons. This one literally has like a
section for features. It has a section
for FAQs. You can get inspiration on how
you want every single like little
element of your site to look, even like
the text, all of the stuff. And then
that's basically part five, which is
understanding what components can you
grab that already exist somewhere that
you can use in order to make your site
feel more dynamic and feel more branded.
And then really the most important thing
at the end of the day besides actually
no number six, you need to make sure it
works on mobile too. It has to look good
on mobile. So many people are looking
you up on mobile, clicking links on
mobile. Make sure it's verified on
mobile. Claude can do that well.
Anyways, the last thing ties into that,
which is verification. Now, by this I
mean have it screenshot everything,
especially when you're doing scroll
animations. have it screenshot frame by
frame or pixel by pixel as it's, you
know, scrolling down. That way, it's
essentially watching a video of how you
will experience it. So, if you don't
have a verification loop, if it's not
taking screenshots and saying, "Oh, wow.
This looks bad. This looks out of
bounds. This color's off. Let me fix
that." Then what are you doing? Now, the
last part of this video was I was going
to run through a bunch of these other
experiments I did between Fable 5 and
Fable 5.1. I had it build a bunch of
different sites for me. As you can see,
I did like, you know, these perk form
sites right here. This one was Fable
5.1. This one was Fable 5. This one was
Fable 5. This one was Fable 5.1. They
just felt very similar. Like none of
them clearly blew the other one out of
the water. They were very similar
because they had the same prompts, the
same assets, the same brand brand
guidelines, excuse me. And they use the
same skill. They all use Scrollcraft.
There was a few minor minor differences,
but not enough for me to be like, "Wow,
Fable 5.1 crushes Fable 5. Those seven
things that I just talked about are more
important than explicitly using which
model." But here's what's interesting.
Around the board, Fable 5.1 was actually
cheaper. Here's an example. Fable 5.1
was 1824. Fable 5 was 2022. Here's
another one where Fable 5.1 was 1452.
Fable 5 was 1467. So, that one's
actually pretty similar. Here's another
one where Fable 5.1 was 1283 and Fable 5
was 2164. Here's another one where Fable
5.1 was 1118 and Fable 5 was 1737. So if
you guys remember in the release blog
they basically said enthropic said hey
you know Fable 5 is going to be 25% more
efficient which is cheaper on some like
you know knowledge work and and regular
type of work and then on heavy agentic
coding and multistep fable 5 might be as
much as 45% cheaper or sorry fable 5.1
might be as much as 45% cheaper than
fable 5 because of how much more
efficient it is with its tokens and so
far that actually is what I've seen out
of all these experiments and all the
knowledge work that I've done you know
all of the experiments and websites that
you guys saw me build but then also a
bunch of testing that I've done on my
own that I haven't showed you guys, I've
only used about 45% of my weekly Fable
limit, which yes, I know a lot of you
guys might think like, oh, that's a lot
for like, you know, 5 to 6 hours of
work, but I've blown through Fable
weekly limit in like 1 to two hours
before just using Fable 5, driving work,
building some things, building some
websites. I was actually really
surprised that I didn't crush through my
weekly Fable limit already, just based
on how much I've been sitting here using
it for the past multiple hours. So
anyways guys, I was going to break that
down more, but honestly I thought that
it would just get a little bit boring
and feel repetitive. So I just wanted to
bring you guys those results. Overall,
Fable 5.1 feels a little bit faster and
a little bit cheaper. But that is going
to do it for today. Don't forget to go
into my free school community linked in
the description if you want that scroll
craft skill because it's what I'm
constantly updating as I'm learning more
about AI design. So if you enjoyed the
video or you learn something new, please
give it a like. It helps me out a ton.
And as always, I appreciate you guys
making it to the end of the video and I
will see you all in the next one. Thanks
everyone.